thefreesextubes.com 2015-04-11

# Privacy Policy

#### Overview

In accordance with this Privacy Policy you consent to the collection, use, disclosure, and processing of your Personal Information every time you visit the site. This includes the transfer of your Personal Information to servers and computer systems anywhere in the world, including to jurisdictions that may not provide the same level of data protection to the laws in your area.

#### Personal Information Collection

We automatically collect Personal Information when you register with the site, send e-mail to our administrator or submit any information to the site. This may include your name, user ID, contact information including e-mail address, and other information that you choose to submit. Before providing Personal Information that relates to another person you hereby state and agree that you have obtained proper consent to do so in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

#### Use of Personal Information

We may use your Personal Information for the following purposes; registration with the site, responses to inquiries, posting submissions to the site, providing information to others regarding your site usage, to alert you to relevant products and services and send newsletters to you when you subscribe to them. We always give you the option to unsubscribe and instructions of how to do so in all communications.

#### Passive Information Collection

Passive information collection on this site includes the monitoring of site visits, including times, dates, pages viewed and other information. This is collected via Internet protocol (IP) addresses, navigational data, including log files and transmission data. We also track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site through the use of tracking technologies. We use this for administration purposes.

#### Cookies

Like many Internet sites, the site may use ‘cookies’ to store a variety of information, including user preferences, passwords, IP addresses, navigational data and server information. You can configure your browser to manage the use of cookies or to disable them. However, disabling cookies may affect your use of the site. 

#### Recording Personal Information

We record personal information such as your name, address and contact details to process and ship orders and provide customer service.

#### Third Parties

We never share, sell, rent, or trade information with third parties for marketing purposes. We may disclose Personal Information to service providers such as those hosting our servers as well as third parties providing technical support, payment and shipping services. All such parties are obligated to comply with privacy terms substantially similar to this Privacy Policy, and to process data in accordance with our instructions.

We may disclose Personal Information for the following reasons: to process orders; to protect the security of the site; to protect ourselves against liability; to protect the health and safety of any third party or to respond to legitimate requests by law enforcement officials. We may also disclose information to the purchaser in connection with any sale, assignment, or other transfer of all or a part of our business or company. In any of these situations, the recipient of the Personal Information may be located in another jurisdiction that may not provide an equivalent level of data protection to the laws in your home jurisdiction.

#### Payment Processing Providers

When you purchase a product, we will share your name, address, credit card details and purchase amount so that the third party can provide the payment processing service. Credit card information is transmitted over a secure SSL-encrypted connection to our payment processor and stored in a PCI Level 1-compliant datacenter until the transaction is completed, at which point it is completely removed unless you request otherwise. We do not store credit card information on our server.

#### Shipping Providers

When shipping an order, we pass contact information to our shipping partner. These companies do not use personally identifiable information for any purposes other than to ship your order.

#### Other Sites

We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit on other web sites, for instance when reviewing our products on blogs or forums. Neither are we responsible for the privacy practices of other sites, including those we may link to. Our privacy statement applies only to information collected on the CaseMyWay site.

#### Accessing Your Information

To access and update Personal Information, please sign into CaseMyWay and click on ‘My Account’.

To exercise any right of rectification, deletion, or opposition to the processing of Personal Information under applicable law, you can also contact us at hello@casemyway.com. We will fulfill your request as appropriate under normal circumstances, but we reserve the right to use Personal Information we have obtained to verify your identity and as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. 

#### Security

We’re committed to offering the highest possible security at all times. We use industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology that encrypts your name, address, your credit card details and any other potentially sensitive information. It ensures that information sent from your computer goes to the correct secure server, that it cannot be read if it’s intercepted and finally it checks that it hasn’t been altered. Despite the fact we use one of the most secure systems available in the world today, Internet transmissions may be subject to error. Therefore we cannot guarantee the security, accuracy, or completeness of Personal Information. 

#### Changes to our policy

If we decide to alter our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and elsewhere on the website. 

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at our sole discretion, except where prior notice or consent is required by law.

Please visit this page and read the Privacy Policy regularly.

#### Third party artwork

CaseMyWay has licensed the right to use all artwork on our site for incorporation into our products. Use of artwork on the site for any other purpose is prohibited. Reproduction of any artwork from CaseMyWay products or from the site is prohibited.
